ultimateplrfiresale.com 2018-01-29

# Privacy Policy

UltimatePLRFiresale.com Privacy Policy

I am committed to keeping all your personal details safe and secure. My privacy policy strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. I carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

**Collecting Your Personal Information**

I am committed to protecting your privacy. I will only use the information that I collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998). I will not pass on your details to any third party and do not send out marketing e-mails unless you have subscribed or registered to receive such material.

**How I Control Your Personal Information**

I will not use your personal information for any other reason other than to contact you. I will never ever sell, give away or rent your email address to any third party.

**How I Use Your Personal Information**

Your personal information is used for 4 main purposes and they are as follows:

1\. To send out information, recommendations and resources to you.  
2\. To provide assistance to you after you have purchased products from me.  
3\. To help me create and deliver content most relevant to you.  
4\. To enlighten you about new products, services, tool, upgrades, special offers and information which I feel may be of use to you.

I will only disclose your personal information, with or without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

(a) Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on UltimatePLRFiresale.com  
(b) Protect and defend the rights or property of UltimatePLRFiresale.com;  
(c) Act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of UltimatePLRFiresale.com.
